https://www.skipsimpson.com/personal-injury/privacy-policy

Home » Personal Injury » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. The purpose of the following statement is to help you understand how our law firm collects, uses and safeguards the personally identifiable information you provide to us on our website.
What information do we collect?
We do not collect any personally identifiable information unless you provide it to us by completing a contact form or by using the live chat feature, or any other online tools. Our goal is to preserve the security of the data you send us when you use any of the online tools provided on this website.
When using our online tools, you may be asked to enter your email address, phone number and name. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To better respond to your individual needs
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To arrange a free consultation with you
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We will not sell any personal information, including your name, email, telephone number and comments, to a third party. Any personally identifiable information and comments submitted through the website will be used for our own purposes. We may provide your information to a trusted third party service provider of this website. We require the service provider to conform to this privacy policy. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third-party links
Some of the pages on this site may include links to external websites. We have included these links for your reference. Please understand that we are not responsible for the external websites' privacy policies, which may differ from our policy.
Online privacy policy
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
FREE Consultation
Contact Us Today
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Download a Printable Version
Download a Printable Version
Related Pages
Suicide
Inpatient Suicide
Mental Health Facilities
Mental Health Malpractice
Psychiatric Malpractice
